Guide to the Grand Street Publications, Inc. Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Editorial Files, 1982-2004
  - Subseries I.3: Author Files, 1989-2004
    - Prose
      - Brenner, Sydney--with Interview on Cassette Tapes, 1998- 1999 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - Breytenbach, Breyten, 1992-1996 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - Brook, Peter, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - Broyard, Bliss, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - Buenel, Luis, 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Burdick, Alan, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Burlingame, Jon, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Burroughs, William--with Proof of My Education, A Book of Dreams, 1989- 1997, (2 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Buzzi, Aldo, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Cabrera Infante, Guillermo, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Cahill, Christopher, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Calvino, Italo, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Canetti, Elias, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Capote, Truman, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Cardoso, Dulce Maria, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Castellanos, Rosario, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Chamoiseau, Patrick, 1992-1997 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Changeux, Jean-Pierre, 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Char, Rene, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Chomsky, Noam, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Cioran, E.M., 1998 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Cisneros, Sandra, 1990-1996 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Cochran, Brian, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Cockburn, Alexander, 1989-1995 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Cohen, Marcelo, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Constantine, Peter, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Cooper, Douglas, 1994-1996 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Cortazar, Julio, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Cross, Brian--Rap Interviews, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 25 to 26)
      - Csoori, Sandor, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - Cvetkovich, Ann, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - Dagerman, Stig, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - Dali, Salvador, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Darvasi, Laszlo, 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      - Davis, Jennifer, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - Davis, Jomo--with Three Floppy Disks, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 33)
      - Davis, Lydia, 1995-1997 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Davis, Mike, 1975-2003, (4 Folders) (Box 54, Folder 2 to 5)
      - Deane, Seamus, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Deanovich, Connie, Undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Death Row, 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - DeLillo, Don--with Images on Compact Disc, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Del Paso, Fernando, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Del Valle-Inclan, Ramon, Undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Diaconu, Alina, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Diasteme, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Dib, Mohammed, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Dongala, Emmanuel, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Duberman, Martin, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Dunne, John Gregory, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Dürrenmatt, Friedrich, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Dunning, A.J., 1992 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Dutch Literature, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - Eco, Umberto, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Egolf, Tristan, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Ellis, Alice Thomas, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Eltit, Diamela, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - Erofeyev, Victor, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - Esterhazy, Peter, Undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - Everson, William K., 1994 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - Fallada, Hans, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Farocki, Harun, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - Feigenbaum, Mitchell, 1993-1994 (Box 54, Folder 31)
      - Feinstein, Elaine, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - Fend, Peter, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      - Feneyrou, Laurent, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Finkelsrein, Caroline, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Fleutiaux, Pierrette, 1989-1991 (Box 54, Folder 36)
      - Frank, Robert, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 37)
      - Franzen, Jonathan, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 38)
      - Friedman, B.H., 1993-1994 (Box 54, Folder 39)
      - Fuentes, Carlos, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 40)
      - Gadda, Carlos Emilio, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 41)
      - Gadda, Carlo Emilio, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 42)
      - Galeano, Eduardo, 1992-1997 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Gao, Xingjian, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      - Garcia Marquez, Gabriel, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 44)
      - Gasdusek, Carleton, 1992-1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Gates, David, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Genet, Jean, 1993-1995, (3 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 4 to 6)
      - Giacometti, Alberto, 1995-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Giddins, Gary, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Goetz, R., 1999 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Gomez de la Serna, Ramon, 1997- 1998 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Gordimer, Nadine, 1991-2003 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Gorz, Andre, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Goswell, Mariana, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Gould, Glenn, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Goytisolo, Juan, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Grand-Guignal, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Grass, Günter, 1997-1999 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Greene, Graham--with Proof of A World of My Own, A Dream Diary, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Green, Henry, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Greene, Merril, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Grunbein, Durs, 1997-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 23 to 24)
      - Gudmundsson, Einar Mar, 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - Guerra, Alberto, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - Guibert, Herve, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 27)
      - Guimaraes Rosa, Joao, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 28)
      - Gunn, Kirsty, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 29)
      - Gursel, Kadri, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Gysin, Brion, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 31)
      - Handke, Peter, 1994-1997 (Box 55, Folder 32)
      - Hansen, Brooks, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 33)
      - Harris, Tomas, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 34)
      - Hatoum, Milton, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 35)
      - Hausser, Alexander, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Heker, Liliana, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Hermann, Judith, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Hilbig, Wolfgang, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Hird, Laura, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Hoai, Pham Thi, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Hoffer, Jen, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Hofmann, Michael, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Hollander, Kurt, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Holper, David, 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Hopper, Dennis--with Floppy Disk, 1994- 1995, (5 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 11 to 15)
      - Hoppes, Felicitas, 1996-1999 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Horn, Stacy, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Howell, Stokes, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Huong, Duong Thu, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Huston, Anjelica, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Huyssen, Andreas, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Iyer, Pico, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Jackson. Shelley, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Jacob, Francois, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - James, Darius, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Jones, Edward P, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Jones, Lloyd, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Jorge, Lidia, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - Jouvet, Louis, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Julia, Edgardo Rodriguez, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - Junger, Ernst, 1998-1999 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      - Kabbani, Nizar, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Kafka, Franz, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - Kamov, J.P., 1995 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Karasu, Bilge, 1995-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Katzir, Yehudit, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Keesey, Anna, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Kerouac, Jack, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Keller, Nora Okja, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Kennedy, Adrienne, Undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Kennedy, A.L., 2003 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Kenny, Maurice, 1985-1989 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Kensinger, Bob, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Kharms, Danil, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Khoury, Elias, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Kienholz, Edward, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Kim, Eleana, Undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Kincaid, Jamaica, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - King, John, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - King, Maryclaire, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Kis, Danilo, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Kluge, Alexander, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Koolhaas, Rem, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Kopkind, Andrew, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - Kovacic, Ivan, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Kovenatsky, Vladimir, 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Kramer, Jane, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Krauss, Angela, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - Krleza, Miroslav, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 28)
      - Kutlar, Onat, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - L.A. Poverty Department, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      - Laughlin, Robert, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - Le, Linda, 1998, (2 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 32 to 33)
      - Leebron, Fred, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 34)
      - Lemebel, Pedro, 1997, (2 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 35 to 36)
      - De Leon, Antonio Garcia, Undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Levy, Deborah, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Llamazares, Julio, 2002-2003 (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Llambias, Pablo Henrik, 1997-1998 (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Lotringer. Sylvere., 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Lovato, Roberto, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 30)
      - Luandino Viera, Jose, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 31)
      - Matoub, Lounes, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - MacKay, Shena, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Mahfouz, Naguib, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Mailer, Norman, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Makanin, Vladimir, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Man, Ray, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Malkovich, John, 1995-1997 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Mamet, David, 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Manganelli, Giorgio, 1996-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 13 to 14)
      - Mann, Thomas, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Marcus, Ben, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Martinez, Ruben, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Martinez, Tomas Eloy, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Mastroianni, Marcello, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Matlock, Jann, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Mekeel McBride, Undated (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Mc Cann, Colum, 1994-1996 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - McKenna, Kristine, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - McPherson, Nina, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - McPherson, Sandra, Undated (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - McWhirter, George, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Mercado, Tununa, 1997-2001 (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - Merewether, Charles, 1997-2003, (4 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 28 to 31)
      - Messiaen, Olivier, 1990-1995 (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - Miano, Sarah Emily, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - Miller, Arthur, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - Milner, Brenda, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - Millhauser, Steven, 1993-1995 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Mohanty, Sharmistha, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Monzo, Quim, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Moody, Rick, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Mora, Terezia, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Morabito, Fabio, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Morrison, Toni, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Muller, Heiner, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Mungan, Murathan, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Munif, Abdelrahman, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Nabokov, Vladimir, 1995-1999 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Nadel, Ira, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Nagy, Peter, Undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Naranjo, Alberto Guerra, 1998-1999, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Newton, Helmut, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Nicholson, Geoff, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Nicholson, Sherry, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Noll, Juao Gilberto, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Nooteboom, Cees, 1999, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Nugent, Beth, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - O’Brien, Geoffrey, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Oe, Kenzaburo, 1990-1997, (5 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 18 to 23)
      - Ogawa, Yoko, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - O’Hagen, Andrew, Undated (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Okri, Ben, 1992-1998 (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Oliva, Peter, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Olney, Richard, Undated (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Onetti, Juan Carlos, 1990-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 29 to 30)
      - Ostermaier, Albert, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - O’Toole, Fintan, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 32)
      - Ozdamar, Emine Sevoi, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 34)
      - Palliser, Charles, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 35)
      - Pamuk, Orhan, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 36)
      - Parei, Inka, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Parker, Alan Michael, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Parks, Suzan-Lori, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Pastior, Oskar, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Paulin, Tom, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Paz, Octavio, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Pekar, Harvey, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 35)
      - Pekarkova, Iva, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Pelevin, Victor, 1995-1998, (4 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 7 to 10)
      - Perec, Georges, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Peri Rossi, Cristina, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Platonov, Andrei, 1991-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 13 to 14)
      - Pohl, Klaus, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Poniatowska, Elena, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Pontiggia, Giuseppe, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Powers, Richard, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Pradier, Hughes, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - Prieto, Jose Manuel, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Printz, Neil, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Proust, Marcel, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Puig, Manuel, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - Pyne, Stephen, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - Quiroga, Horacio, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - Quabbani, Nizar, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - Redgrave, Vanessa, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - Rey Rosa, Rodrigo, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 29)
      - Ribeiro, Edgard Telles, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - Ribeiro, Joao Ubaldo, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - Ribeyro, Julio Ramon, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - Richardson, Tony, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 33)
      - Richman, Jan, 1990-1991 (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - Rimanelli, David, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - Robertson, Deborah, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - Rodriguez, Luis, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - Rofihe, Rick, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - Roth, Joseph, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 39)
      - Rothenburg, Daniel, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - Rulfo, Juan, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 41)
      - Ruscha, Danna, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 42)
      - Rushdie, Salman, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 43)
      - Said, Edward, 1991-2002, (2 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 44 to 45)
      - Said, Edward, 1990-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Salamun. Tomaz, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Sanchez, Luis Rafael, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Saramago, Jose, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Saro-Wiwa, Ken,1995 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Savii, Milisav, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Scheepers, Rianna, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Schmidt, Arno, 1994-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 9 to 10)
      - School of the Americas, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Schuhl, Jean-Jacques, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Schulze, Ingo, 1997-2000 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Schwitters, Kurt, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Searcy, David, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Seesequasis, Paul, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Sellars, Peter, 1996-1997 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Seneca, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Sepulveda, Luis, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Sforza, Cavalli, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Shafak, Elif, 2001-2003 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Shaw, Fiona, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Shields, David, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Smith, Ali, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Smith, R.J., 1997 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Smock, Frederick, 1990-1992 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Solnit, Rebecca, 1995-1997 (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - Sonnenberg, Ben, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 28)
      - Sorokin, Vladimir, 1993-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 29 to 30)
      - Southern, Terry, 1992-1998, (5 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 2 to 6)
      - Stadler, Matthew, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Stein, Jean, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Szarkowski, John, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Tabucchi, Antonio, 1989-2004, (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 10 to 11)
      - Tan, Amy, Undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Tanizaki, Juniochiro, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Tario, Francisco, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Tarkovsky, Andrei, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Tarn, Nathaniel, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Tekin, Latife, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Thomas, Lewis, Undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Thorne, Kip, 1993-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 19 to 20)
      - Tomeo, Javier, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - Tondelli, Pier Vittorio, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - Trebay, Guy, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - Trombley, Stephen, 1992-2003 (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - Ugresic, Dubravka, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 25)
      - Unger, K.S., 1993 (Box 62, Folder 26)
      - Varese, Edgard, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 27)
      - Venturi, Robert, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 28)
      - Veronesi, Sandro, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Vidal, Gore, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Villa-Matas, Enrique, 2001, (2 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Villoro, Juan, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Virilio, Paul, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Vladislavic, Ivan, 1993-1995 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Vollman, William, (8 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 8 to 15)
      - Waberi, Abdourahman A., 2001-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 16 to 17)
      - Wade, Sidney, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Wainwright, Jeffrey, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Walker, Lisa, Undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Wallace, David Foster, 1995-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 21 to 22)
      - Walser, David, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - Walser, Martin, Undated (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - Warner, Alan, 1996-2002 (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - Wastberg, Per, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Waters, John, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Weil, Andrew T., 1993 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Weinberger, Eliot, 1991-1999 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Weiss, Peter, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Welles, Orson, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Welsh, Irvine, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Weschler, Lawrence, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Wexler, Alice, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - White, Edmund, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Wideman, John, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Wilkinson, Alec, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Williams, Sarah, Undated-1999, (2 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Williams, Tennessee, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Williams, Terry, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Wills, Garry, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Wilson, Robert McLiam, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Winterson, Jeanette, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Wolf, Christa, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Wright, Ronald, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Xue, Can, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Y.B., 1998 (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - Yoshimura, Akira, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Yunus, Muhammad, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Zadek, Peter, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - Zischler, Hans, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 29)
      - Zonabend, Francoise--includes Copy of La Presqu’Ile au Nucleaire with Notes, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Subseries I.4: Supplementary Editorial Materials, 1990-2003 (Box 74)
    This small subseries contains some unused submissions, reader responses and editorial ideas for potential stories and authors for Grand Street. Unused submissions are arranged alphabetically by author and include rejections and materials published by the author in other venues. Story ideas include brainstorming sessions from editorial meetings, lists of prospective authors to work with and correspondence with authors approached to write "dispatches" columns from different regions for Grand Street's website.
    - Unused Submissions
      - General--Artists, 1996- 2000, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 5 to 6)
      - General--Writers, 1994-1999 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Anagrama, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - Baudrillard, Jean, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Brenner, Sydney, Undated (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Carton, Ben, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Chang, Ta-Chun--Includes Floppy Disk, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Dal, Guney, Undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - Golding, Paul, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Greene, James, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Grondahl, Jens Cristian, Undated (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Hayden, Tom, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Hecht, David, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Jackson, Shelley, 2000s (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - Jorge, Lidia, Undated (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - King, Mary-Claire, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Konigsberg, Eric, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - Kovenatsky, Rachel, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - Kushma, Yayoi, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Linfield, Susie, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - Lipsyte, Sam, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - Marcus, Ben (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Marques, Rafael, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - Mendes, Pedro Rosa, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Michaux, Henri, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - Ozdamar, Emine Sevgi, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 37)
      - Parla, Jale, Undated (Box 73, Folder 38)
      - Pisigin, Valery, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 39)
      - Pound, Ezra, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 40)
      - Reimann, Brigette, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 41)
      - Rivas, Manuel, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 42)
      - Saramago, Jose, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 43)
      - Sebald, W.G., 2002 (Box 73, Folder 44)
      - Smith, Zadie, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 45)
      - Sorokobi, Yves, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 46)
      - Stage, Jan, Undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Tabucchi, Antonio, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Vallejo, Fernando (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Vollmann, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Walser, Robert, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Reader Responses, 1995-2002, (5 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 8 to 15)
    - Story Ideas
      - General, 1990-2000, (21 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 6 to 29, and 41)
      - Walter Hopps, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 37)
      - Jean Stein, 1989-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 30 to 31)
      - Jeremy Treglow, 1991- 1993 (Box 75, Folder 36)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1981-2000
  Letters, postcards and notes from authors, editors and agents are included within this series. Correspondents include Anne Carson, Noam Chomsky, Arthur Danto, Ted Hughes, Joyce Carol Oates, Edward Said and Virgil Thomson. The correspondence is arranged in two subseries: correspondence from authors and correspondence from editors and agents.
  - Subseries II.1: Authors, 1981-1990
    Ben Sonnenberg's editorial correspondence with authors is included within this subseries. Most correspondence pertains to preparations for the author's inclusion in Grand Street, however, as Sonnenberg knew and nurtured many of these authors, letters often touch upon personal matters as well. Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by last name and then is generally organized chronologically within folders. This subseries is further divided into previously catalogued and non-catalogued correspondence, which reflects the decision to catalogue some materials upon their acquisition. The original alphabetical arrangement of non-catalogued material has been retained.